export const dataForName = {
    totalQuestions: 20,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'CB5',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'C4',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'B5',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Beijing Beef',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'C3',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Kung Pao Chicken',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'V1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Super Greens',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'B1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'BROCCOLI BEEF',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'F4',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'HONEY WALNUT SHRIMP',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'C1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'The Original Chicken',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'CB1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'String Bean Chicken Beast',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'C2',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Mushroom Chicken',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'B3',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Black Pepper Augus Steak',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'R2',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'White Steamed Rice',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: 'M1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Chow Mein',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: 'R1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Fried Rice',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: 'E1',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Vegetable Spring Roll',
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: 'C9',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Blazing Boubon Chicken',
      },
      {
        id: 17,
        question: 'E5',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Apple Pie Roll',
      },
      {
        id: 18,
        question: 'E2',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Chicken Egg Roll',
      },
      {
        id: 19,
        question: 'E3',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Cream Cheese Rangoons',
      },
      {
        id: 20,
        question: 'CB3',
        answers: ['The Original Chicken', 'Broccoli Beef', 'Honey Walnut Shrimp', 'String Bean Chicken Beast', 'Beijing Beef', 'Grilled Teriyaki Chicken', 'Kung Pao Chicken', 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast', 'Mushroom Chicken', 'Black Pepper Augus Steak', 'Chicken Egg Roll', 'Vegetable Spring Roll', 'Cream Cheese Rangoons', 'Apple Pie Roll', 'Blazing Boubon Chicken', 'Sweet Fire Chicken Breast', 'Chow Mein', 'Fried Rice', 'Super Greens', 'White Steamed Rice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Honey Sesame Chicken Breast',
      },
    ],
  };
  